https://www.adventures-abroad.com/privacy-policy

Contact
Covid-19 update: Review our new Tour Care & Safety Protocols How to contact us during Covid-19
Our Privacy Policy
SEARCH TOUR
We respect your concerns about privacy. We use, as well as pass on to our suppliers/operators, information provided by you to ensure your travel arrangements run smoothly and in accordance with your requirements.
+Booking Information
This information may include: name; address; age; any special needs, disabilities, dietary requirements, etc. We take full responsibility for ensuring that proper security measures protect your information. We must pass this information to relevant suppliers for your travel arrangements, such as airlines, hotels, transport companies, etc. This information may also be provided to public authorities, such as customs/immigration, if required by law.
+E-mail Newsletter Registration
When you ask to receive our newsletter (eNavigator), you provide us with information with which we can fulfil your request and even personalize our mailings. We will send you details concerning our products, services and promotions using this information, but this information will not be used by a third party.
+Contest Participation
When entering our contests, you send us information that allows us to enter you into contests, verify eligibility and contact you if you win. We will also use this information to send you details concerning our products, services and promotions, unless you specifically opt-out from receiving such details when you enter.
+Updating the Privacy Policy
Changing information practices may warrant our updating our privacy policy. As a result, we recommend periodical privacy policy reviews. Your continued use of the site indicates your consent to such terms.
+E-mail Newsletter Unsubscribe
We will remove any personal information from our database should you so desire by way of written request. Please e-mail such requests to sales@adventures-abroad.com, identifying your full name. Make sure the subject line reads "unsubscribe."
+For United Kingdom Passengers
You should be aware that where your holiday destination lies outside the European Economic Area (EEA), controls on data protection might not be as strong as legal requirements in the UK. When you provide us with sensitive information, such as details of dietary/religious requirements, you consent to this information being passed to relevant suppliers. Once your information is passed, suppliers adhere to their own data protection policies.
+Promotional Photographs
Occasionally, we will use photographs taken by fellow guests or your Tour Leader on your tour for promotional purposes. If you prefer that your photo not be used in any marketing activities, please notify your Tour Leader at the start of your tour.
ONLINE CATALOGUE
View our catalogue today!
Copyright © Adventures Abroad Worldwide Travel Ltd., All Rights Reserved
Title *:
Mr
Mrs
Miss
Ms
First Name *:
Last Name *:
Email Address *:
Country of Interest (optional):
Newsletters are sent approximately once a month; we never rent or sell our mailing list. See our Privacy Policy for further details.
SIGN UP FOR NEWSLETTER
Thank you!
Your inquiry has been sent to us successfully.
Someone will contact you very soon.
Please check your inbox for the email.
If the email is not present there, please check your junk mail folder and mark the email as 'not junk'.
If you are still experiencing problems or the email is nowhere to be found, please Contact Us
CLOSE
We're Sorry
Your inquiry has not been sent to us.
Please try again.
BACK
You are about to open a webpage not part of the Adventures Abroad website, would you like to continue?
Cancel
Continue
